很开心你安全回来了
I'm glad to see you made it safely.
酒店怎么样?
How's your hotel?
这并不是我住过的最好的百维顿酒店
It's not the best Best Western I've been to,
但差不多是...
but I'd say it's...
我去过第三好的百维顿酒店
the third best Best Western I've been to.
我懂
I know how you feel.
我家附近的百思买是第三好的百思买
The Best Buy by my house is only the third best Best Buy.
他们有百思买
They have the best buys,
Bestbuy是美国电子产品零售商, 中文为百思买, Best意为最好的, 此处为双关
但如果只是几百种货物便宜点
but having the best buys isn't the only thing
还不足以让它被称为最好的百思买
that makes a Best Buy the best Best Buy.
那什么才能让一个百思买成为最好的百思买?
What makes a best Best Buy the best Best Buy?
嗯 这问题问得好
Mm, that's a great question.
美国知名墨西哥卷饼店
如果他开在Chipotle旁边的话我会喜欢
I like when they're next to a Chipotle.
嗯 我得去整理行李了
Okay, well, I should unpack.
好吧
All right.
享受你的神经生物学研讨会吧
Enjoy the neurobiology conference.
我会的
I will.
我... 希望你能在这
I... wish you were here.
在这个神经生物学研讨会上吗?
At a neurobiology conference?
这是什么话?
What a mean thing to say.
嗯 我很开心你不在这里?
Okay, I'm glad you're not here?
啊 每次我一告诉你该怎么说
Aw, you always know just what to say
你就知道该怎么说了
after I tell you what to say.
再见 Sheldon
Good-bye, Sheldon.
再见
Bye.
哦 好消息 先生们
Oh! Good news, gentlemen.
Amy这周末去参加了一个研讨会
Amy's at a conference this weekend,
也就是说我可以娱乐了
which means I'm available to be entertained, hmm.
就像现在小年轻们说的: 谁带我浪一浪?
As today's youth might put it: Who wants to get their Sheld-on?
Bernie和我在准备给房子进行改造
Bernie and I are getting the house ready for the remodel.
多个人帮忙总是好事
We could always use an extra pair of hands.
好无聊 Raj?
That sounds awful. Raj?
嗯 我预约了这周末的望远镜室
Uh, I've got time booked in the telescope room all weekend
来寻找星际行星
scanning for rogue planets.
很欢迎你加入我
You're more than welcome to join me.
这个有待考虑 Leonard?
That's the one to beat. Leonard?
啊 我打算不带你浪
Oh, if anything, I'm trying to get my Sheld-off.
嗯 看来有人胜出了 祝贺你
Well, then it looks like we have a winner. Congratulations.
嗯 我应该警告你的 其实只是
Well, I should warn you, it's just looking at data
盯着电脑屏幕上的数据不停地看
for hours and hours on a computer screen.
嗯 不用推销了 你赢了
Uh, stop selling it, kid. You won.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第12集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
校对: UUUU吃吃吃吃
协调: 不想复习的酥酥
翻译: 肉肉君 黑脸猫呗 小黄不小黄 無限月讀 娘娘爱酥酥
大家好
Hey.
- 你好  - 好啊
- Hey.  - Hello.
嘿 你今天过的怎么样?
Hi. How was your day?
哦 不太好
Oh, not good.
还是见不到Gallo医生
Still couldn't get in to see Dr. Gallo.
医生?
A doctor?
希望你得的不是传染性的
Well, I hope you're not contagious.
我这周末准备待在望远镜室里
I've got a weekend in the telescope room
我已经激动了三分钟了
I've been excited about for almost three minutes.
我没生病 是为了工作
I'm not sick. It's for work.
这个医生一个药品推销员都不想见
There's this doctor who refuses to see any sales reps.
我已经试着接触他好几个月了
I've been trying to get in for months.
你试过穿那件
Well, did you try wearing the shirt
我说不适合穿去上班的衬衫了吗?
I said was inappropriate for work?
嗯 这个医生是女的 但...
Well, the doctor's a woman, but...
我穿了 什么样的人都有
yes, because you never know.
她是什么样的医生?
What kind of doctor is she?
嗯 一个精神科医生 怎么了?
Um, a psychiatrist. Why?
如果你假装病人预约她来看病呢?
Well, what if you make an appointment as a patient?
这样你就能和她说话了
Then you'll get to talk to her.
他们已经知道我是药品推销员了
Yeah, they already know I'm a pharmaceutical sales rep.
哦 那如果Leonard预约
Oh. What if Leonard made an appointment
然后给你打好铺垫呢?
and tried to lay some groundwork for you?
有意思
That's interesting.
我才不和精神科医生
I'm not gonna make a fake appointment
做假预约呢
with a psychiatrist.
我有什么毛病?
What would I say is wrong with me?
- 低自尊心  - 社交恐惧
- Low self-esteem.  - Social anxiety.
性不安全感
Sexual insecurity.
这都不对
None of that is true.
否认 看啊 我还能说出一大堆
Uh, denial. See, sweetie, the list goes on and on.
太扯了
That's just crazy.
我进去后能帮你什么忙?
How would my going in there even help you?
我不知道啊 你可以和她说话啊 如果她提起来的话
I don't know. You could talk to her, and maybe if it comes up,
你可以问问她听没听说过这个药
you could ask if she's heard about the drug.
如果我被揭穿怎么办?
What if I get caught?
畏惧失败! 缺乏自信!
Fear of failure! Lack of confidence!
胆小鬼!
Kind of a wuss!
好吧 我去
Fine, I'll do it.
但是不是因为他们 而是因为我爱你
But not because of them, because I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 墙头草  - 没骨气
- Pushover.  - Spineless.
两天前就和他说过的牛奶
Still hasn't bought milk
到今天都没买回来!
even though I told him two days ago!
真是无与伦比啊
That was incredible.
是啊
It was.
我只希望Stuart不在这
I just wish Stuart wasn't around
我们就不用这么小声了
so we didn't have to be so quiet.
同感
I know.
他看日本色情动漫时
It's not like he returns the favor
也完全不在意一下我们的感受
when he watches his Japanese porn cartoons.
你俩有空吗
You guys got a minute,
还是正后戏拥抱着呢?
or are you still cuddling?
怎么了 Stuart?
What is it, Stuart?
我能进门吗?
Can I come in?
等一下
Hang on.
要不要把他赶走?
Should I send him away?
不用 没事的
No, it's okay.
谢谢 Bernie
Thanks, Bernie.
怎么了?
What's up?
我知道
Uh, well, I know
我知道你们要重新装修了 所以为了让你们容易点
the remodel is coming up, so I thought I'd make it easy
是时候找个自己的住处了
on you guys and find my own place.
哇
Wow.
我还以为今天的高潮已经过去了呢
I thought I was done getting lucky tonight.
你准备什么时候搬出去啊?
So, when are you thinking of moving?
实际上 我已经找到公寓了
Uh, actually, I already found an apartment,
所以就这几天吧
so in a couple of days.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
听到你要离开 很抱歉?
Sorry to see you go?
总之 谢谢你俩为我做的一切
Okay, well, thank you guys for everything.
我... 我非常感谢你们
I... I really appreciate it.
一点也不用谢
You're very welcome.
怎么了?
What?
你俩醒着的时候 我还没来过这房间呢
Hmm, I just have never been in this room while you're awake.
你在干啥呢?
What are you doing?
调节望远镜摄像头的白平衡
Uh, making sure the telescope's camera is white-field balanced.
你现在又在干啥呢?
What are you doing now?
还是在调节望远镜摄像头的
Still making sure the telescope's camera
- 白平衡  - 酱紫啊
- is white-field balanced.  - Oh, I see.
那现在呢?
How about now?
现在我在调节望远镜摄像头的
Now I'm making sure the telescope's camera
白平衡 而且希望你能有个填色本打发时间
is white-field balanced and wishing you had a coloring book.
我可以帮你的忙啊
Well, I can be helpful.
找点事情给我做吧
Give me something to do.
有次我爸爸带我去上班
You know, my father took me to work once,
而十分钟之内我就发现
and in ten minutes I figured out
一直以来谁在收银机里偷钱了
who'd been stealing from the cash register.
就是我爸爸
It was my father.
虽然我爸爸失业了
Yeah, Dad lost his job,
但是Hinckley先生给了我一根巧克力棒
but Mr. Hinckley gave me a Fudgsicle.
好吧 你想做事吗?
Fine, you want something to do?
这个硬盘里有六个月的数据
There's about six months of data on this hard drive.
你慢慢审阅一遍 看看能不能找到
Why don't you go through it and see if you can spot
有什么模式或者异常
any patterns or anomalies.
行 让我来吧 嘿 瞧瞧啊!
Yep, I'm on it. Hey, look at that!
一个印度人在给白人分配电脑任务
An Indian guy outsourcing a computer job to a white fella.
行吧 不管怎样
Yeah, okay, whatever it takes
这事能让你忙几个小时的
to keep you busy for a few hours.
找到一个了
Found one.
你才没有呢
No, you didn't.
这里面有数百万的数据点呢
There are millions of data points there.
但是你看呀 这是光学瞬态
But, look, an optical transient.
的确 还真给你找到了
Yeah, maybe that is something.
- 你怎么找到的?  - 这不难的
- How did you find that?  - It wasn't difficult.
你知不知道 看到质数的时候 它们是红色的
You know how when you see prime numbers, they appear red,
而孪生素数
but when they're twin primes,
就是粉色的 还有汽油味儿?
they're pink and smell like gasoline?
没听说过
No.
那就是我天赋异禀吧
Oh. I guess I'm a special boy.
一般遇到天赋异禀的男孩
You know, sometimes when a boy is special,
别人会给他巧克力棒吃的
he gets a Fudgsicle.
而且 尝起来犹如光速
Which, by the way, tastes like the speed of light.
临时通知还能见到你 太感谢了
Thank you for seeing me on such short notice.
不用谢
Ah, it's my pleasure.
我很好奇
I'm curious,
你和Beverly Hofstadter博士有亲属关系吗?
are you related to Dr. Beverly Hofstadter?
她是我的母亲 你认识她吗?
Uh, she's my mother. You know her?
不 没有见过面
No, not personally,
但是我读过她的书
but I have read all of her books.
好吧 那估计你比我更了解她了
Well, then you know her better than I do.
这我可不敢说
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
但我跟你说
But I can tell you I do not agree
我完全不认同她的育儿理论
with her theories on child rearing at all.
真的吗?
Really?
你是觉得它们太冷酷 太残忍
Any chance you find them cold, cruel and unsuitable
根本不适合一个只想过得开心的小男孩吗?
for innocent little boys who just want to be happy?
其实我不想多说的...
Well, I didn't want to say it...
没关系 说吧 唱出来都行
No, no, say it. Sing it.
租一架飞机 写在天上
Rent a plane, write it in the sky.
看来你心中
Sounds like you're holding on
对她非常不满啊
to quite a bit of anger towards her.
没有 我在这方面
Oh, no, I've worked through
下过不少功夫 我现在已经好多了
a lot of that stuff; I'm better now.
嗯 真不错
Mm. Good for you.
你知道吗 她从来不让我过生日
Do you know she never let me
因为她觉得我出生
celebrate my birthday because being born
是她的功劳 和我没关系?
was her achievement, not mine?
真是令人心碎
That's heartbreaking.
对吧? 到现在了我每年生日还会给她寄一张贺卡
Right? To this day, I send her a card every year
里面还夹点钱
with a little money in it.
等到我们搬回来的时候
You know, once we get the house back to ourselves,
我们就可以到处浪漫了
we can be romantic in any room we want.
太好了 我终于可以带你去看洗衣房了
Great. I can finally show you where the laundry room is.
当初你让我搬进来
Boy, who would've thought
照顾你妈妈的时候 谁能想到
when you asked me to move in and help take care of your mom,
我在这里待了整整两年?
I'd still be here two years later?
- 没人想得到  - 没人
- Nobody thought that.  - No one.
就这样了
Well, that's it.
是啊
I guess so.
这感觉真奇怪
This is weird.
是啊 一个成年人要搬回自己家了
Yeah. A grown man moving into his own apartment.
太疯狂了 再见!
Crazy times. See ya!
别管他
Ignore him.
他只是靠开玩笑来表达...
He's just using humor to express how...
他的喜悦
happy he is.
没事 我知道他是爱我的
It's okay. I know he loves me.
当然
Sure he does.
等到你安顿好了告诉我们一声
Well, let us know when you're all settled in.
我会的 真是感激不尽
I will. And I really can't thank you guys enough.
不用谢
Our pleasure.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye.  - Bye.
他走啦!
He's gone!
我们从车库开始吧!
Let's start in the garage!
好的 等到我们收到下一个图像
Okay, so once we receive the next image
把它和我们现有的图像做对比
and compare it to the ones we've already collected,
我们就知道我们发现的是什么了
we'll know what it is that we found.
哦 可能是日鞘闪烁
Ooh, perhaps it's a Heliosheath scintillation.
也有可能是一个海王星外天体
It could be a trans-Neptunian object.
可能是一个新的行星
Maybe it's a new planet.
不太可能 不过它有可能是一个矮行星
Unlikely, but it could be a dwarf planet.
只要它的引力正常
Well, as long as it has a healthy gravity
还有卫星 我就满足了
and all its moons, I'll be happy.
好吧 最后的图像收到了
Okay, the final image is coming in.
我们发现的东西是...
And the object we discovered is...
加油
Come on,
爸爸要用铁腕统治星球了
Daddy needs a livable planet he can rule with an iron fist.
一个中等大小的小行星
A medium-sized asteroid.
就这么点?
That's it?
太平常了
How common.
就好像是宇宙的菜单上那道上校鸡块
That's the chicken fingers on the menu of space.
我挺喜欢上校鸡块的
I kind of like chicken fingers.
我也是 我只是不知道怎么比喻了
Yeah, me, too. I was stuck for a metaphor.
算了吧 一个中等大小的小行星
Come on, a medium-sized asteroid
也算是有趣的发现了
is still an interesting discovery.
我想它也许会
I suppose it could end up
撞向地球 毁灭一切生物吧
on a collision course with Earth and destroy life as we know it.
你的梦和我的真的不太一样
You dream different than me.
真可爱
It is kind of cute.
是啊 而且我们可以给它取名字了
Yeah, it is. And you know we get to name it.
我们最好取一个别人不会笑话的名字
We better choose a name no one can make fun of.
"天王星"在英文中与"撒尿"很像
弗里德里希·威廉·赫歇尔爵士给天王星取的这个名字可太难听了
Sir Frederick William Herschel didn't do Uranus any favors.
嗨
Hi.
- 嘿 那件事顺利吗?  - 很棒
- Hey, how'd it go?  - Oh, great.
Gallo医生太棒了
Dr. Gallo is terrific.
我... 我一直有一种不安全感
You know, I... I've always been insecure
以为别人都不在乎我想说什么
that no one cares about what I have to say,
但是她让我看到了...
but she made me see...
是没人在乎 你到底帮我了没有?
Yeah, no one cares. Did you help me out or not?
好吧 我知道
Okay, n-now, what I'm hearing
你感觉我有时候花太多时间
is that you feel that I sometimes take too long
表达我自己了
to express myself,
你希望我能说话简洁一点
and you wish I'd be more succinct.
你知道是因为我
You're only hearing that because
翻白眼都翻出声音来了
I cannot roll my eyes any louder.
好吧 就在我们谈论过我和我母亲的问题之后...
All right, well, after we talked about my issues with my mother...
没那么深入 只是她怎么毁了我的生活...
nothing too deep, just how she ruined my life...
我跟她讲了你还有你的药物
I told her about you
她说她很乐意见你
and your drug; she said she'd be happy to meet you.
真的
Really?
噢 你是最棒的老公!
Oh, you're the best husband ever!
所以你下周要陪我去神秘博士大会了?
So you'll go to the Doctor Who convention with me next week?
我想是吧
I guess.
这次我的确听见你翻白眼了
Oh, I actually did hear your eyes roll that time.
天啊 Stuart上次打扫这个地方是什么时候的事了?
Boy, when was the last time Stuart cleaned this place?
不开玩笑
No kidding.
我要把一些脏东西吸起来了
Oh, okay, I'm about to suck something up.
你觉得这东西听起来像什么?
What do you think this object sounds like?
Howie 我不想再玩"积木指甲还是药片"的游戏了
Howie, I don't want to play Lego, Toenail or Pill anymore.
你觉得我们该拿这个房间怎么办?
So, what do you think we should do with this room?
我考虑过家庭影院或者游戏室...
Well, I was thinking a home theater or a gaming room...
你看 就像男人的窝
you know, like a man cave.
为什么不能是女人的窝?
Why can't it be a woman cave?
只要这房里有家庭影院 游戏机
As long as it has a home theater, a video game system
而你也不许进来
and you're not allowed in it,
那么你爱叫它什么都可以
you can call it whatever you want.
我说认真的
I'm being serious.
那你觉得我们该怎么办?
Well, what do you think we should do?
我不知道
I don't know,
也许装成家庭办公室或者...
maybe a home office or...
噢
Oh.
看啊
Look.
我们带Stuart去夜市那晚他赢回来的泰迪熊
The teddy bear Stuart won the night we took him to the fair.
噢
Oh.
他可兴奋了
He was so excited.
是啊
Yeah.
无论他们想什么办法
You know, no matter how hard they tried,
都猜不出他的年纪
they could not guess his age.
下次看见他的时候我带给他
I'll give it to him next time I see him.
自从他走后你有他的消息吗?
Have you heard from him since he left?
没有
No.
还以为一旦他安顿下来就会给我们打电话的
You'd think he would've called once he got settled in.
也许他忙着呢
Hmm. Maybe he's busy.
没时间打电话? 他可有时间
Too busy to call? He wasn't too busy
用我Hulu网站的密码看 魅力克利夫兰
to binge-watch Hot in Cleveland with my Hulu password.
怎么回事?
What is happening?
我们想他了吗?
Are we missing him?
不是 这种感觉不是想他
No, that's not what this feeling is.
是想他吗?
Is it?
当然不是 他把我们逼疯了
Of course not. He drove us crazy.
像上次你要做一个派
Like when you were gonna make that pie
结果Stuart提前吃光了所有的蓝莓
and Stuart ate all the blueberries.
他还想不承认 可他的牙都是紫的
And he tried to deny it, but his teeth were all purple.
太可爱了
That was pretty cute.
是啊
Yeah.
恶... 我们想他了!
Ew, we are missing him!
我在考虑 也许我们可以通过把咱俩的名字连起来
So I was thinking, maybe we can come up with a name
来给这个小行星起名字
for the asteroid by combining our names.
这个想法不错
That's a great idea.
我想到了
I've got it.
我们叫它... Cooper
We'll call it... Cooper.
不是说咱们俩的名字吗?
How is that both our names?
Koothrappali的Koo Cooper的per
"Koo" from Koothrappali and "per" from Cooper.
那么 就像是 K开头的Kooper?
Yeah, so... so it's, like, Kooper with a "K"?
你说得对 那个太傻了
Nah, you're right, that's dumb.
嘿
Hey.
Leopard 好消息
Oh, Leonard, great news.
我们一起发现了一个中型小行星
We discovered a medium-sized asteroid together.
哇 太棒了!
Wow, that's amazing!
我今儿也心情不错
I'm in a pretty great mood today myself.
好了 想来现在我们要谈你的事情了
Okay. Guess we're gonna talk about you now.
是的 因为Gallo医生让我意识到
Well, we are, because Dr. Gallo made me realize
我是个有价值的人而且我的感受很重要
that I'm a worthwhile person and that my feelings matter.
网上那些猫图早就让我免费了解到了 可还是给你赞一个
I learned that for free from a cat poster, but good for you.
好了 讲讲我的事情
Okay, back to me.
我发现了一个小行星 现在得给他命名
I discovered an asteroid, and now I get to name it.
等等 说好的我们呢?
Wait, what happened to us?
现在 这不是关于我们
Now, this isn't about us,
而是关于怎样才对小行星最好
this is about what's best for the asteroid.
你考虑怎么命名?
What are you thinking of naming it?
我还没做任何决定
I haven't settled on anything yet.
我们还没做任何决定
We haven't settled on anything yet.
好了 猫图 你坚持住啊
All right, way to go, Cat Poster. You hang in there.
知道怎样最好吗?用你们的女朋友给它命名
You know what'd be nice? Name it after your girlfriends.
让她们了解有多在乎她们
Show them how much you care.
这个主意太棒了
That is a great idea.
完美
It's perfect.
看起来很浪漫
It appears romantic, but it's really just
可只是一块太空里
a rock in space that gets me
能让我永远摆脱麻烦的情人节的石头而已
out of Valentine's Day forever.
所以 呃 你觉得呢? 把她们的名字合起来?
So, uh, what were you thinking? Combine their names?
我觉得不错
I like it.
所以说我们取Amy的”A和M”然后
Yeah, we'll take the "AM" from Amy and, uh,
取Emily的”Y”
the "Y" from Emily.
那合起来还是Amy啊
That's just Amy.
正是 看见我们配合的多好了吗?
Exactly. See how well we work together?
双盲实验里证明了
And in double-blind studies,
Placinex对于各种焦虑症
Placinex proved extremely effective in treating
都有超级好的疗效
all kinds of anxiety.
跟你说实话吧 真是太有意思了… 实验小哥
Actually, funny story… the boys in the lab
特别担心Placinex是不是能取得药监局认证
were worried about getting FDA approval for Placinex;
然后他们吃了那个药 就一点都不担心了
they started taking it, stopped worrying.
知道了
Got it.
呃 你还有什么问题吗?
Uh, do you have any questions?
- 就一个  - 什么?
- Just one.  - Mm-hmm?
你让你老公假装病人
When you made your husband pretend to be a patient
给你探路的时候 你想什么呢?
so you could get access to me, what were you thinking there?
我是说… 你有什么关于这种药的问题吗
I just… meant a question about the drug.
我知道你什么意思
Yeah, I know what you meant.
不过现在先不谈那个
Let's put that aside for a minute
咱们来说说你为什么嫁给了Leonard吧
and talk about why you married Leonard.
我也不想…
I don't wanna…
这么多年 这个男人被强势的妈
Here is a man raised by an overbearing woman
统治了生活的方方面面
who completely dominated every aspect of his formative years.
你觉不觉得
Do you think
他找你做老婆
he's perpetuating that relationship
是为了延续那样的关系?
by seeking out a partner like you?
说起来 我以前经常穿吊带背心
You know, I used to wear tank tops a lot.
估计这个才是重点吧
That was a big selling point.
嘿 Sheldon 怎么啦?
Hi, Sheldon. What's up?
有好消息 你是一颗小行星啦
Good news. You're an asteroid.
呃… 我不太知道应该说什么了
Uh… please tell me what to say next.
我应该给你解释一下
Perhaps I should explain.
我和Koothrappali一起工作的时候
While working with Koothrappali,
发现了一颗小行星 然后我用你的名字给它命名了
we discovered an asteroid, and I named it after you.
哦
Oh.
Sheldon 人家好喜欢
Sheldon, thank you.
真是太浪漫啦
That's so romantic.
那Rajesh呢?
But what about Rajesh?
你选了名字他同意吗?
He was okay with you choosing the name?
这个嘛 我跟他协商了一下
Well, it took a little negotiating,
然后我把他说服了
but I wore him down.
所以呢 我们来命名小行星
Uh, we get the asteroid,
但是如果我们以后有了孩子
and if you and I have children,
他们都得叫Rajesh
they all have to be named Rajesh.
所有孩子吗?
All of them?
连女孩也是
Even the girls.
现在我知道我想说什么了
Okay, I think I know what to say now.
我们的卧室全都铺满了星球大战的玩具
How can I not sound like his mother
我怎么可能不像他妈妈一样说他?
when our entire bedroom is filled with Star Wars toys?
我是说 你肯定没在毛绒伍基人
I mean, have you ever had sex
瞪着你的时候啪啪啪过吧?
with a stuffed Wookiee watching you?
我可是七十年代上的大学 大家都不脱毛
I went to college in the '70s; it was a hairier time.
我觉得肯定有过
I'm gonna say yes.
总之 更像是他把我慢慢变成了他妈
You know, if anything, he's turning me into his mother.
做医药代表之前 我是个演员
Before I did pharmaceutical sales, I was an actress.
我还干得不错呢
You know, I was pretty good.
你知道的 就是邻家女孩那种类型的 但是超性感哟
You know, girl-next-door type, but hot.
那种容易被上的
Doable.
诶
Hmm.
而且我还不仅是Leonard的妈
And not only am I Leonard's mother,
我们家还住着一个永远长不大的孩子叫Sheldon
but we have this man-child living with us named Sheldon.
哦 Leonard经常说起他
Oh, Leonard talked a lot about him.
我还以为那是他自己想出来的呢
I wasn't sure if he was real.
我倒希望是 我要是用多了厕所手纸
Yeah, he's as real as the fine I get
还得给他交罚款呢
when I use too much toilet paper.
天哪 你有好多烦心事啊
Wow, you really do have a lot on your plate.
是啊
I do.
我觉得
You know,
Leonard说得对
Leonard's right.
跟你说说话确实挺有用的
Talking to you is really helping.
哦 我很高兴
Oh, I'm glad.
知道吗 吃点治焦虑症的药
You know, you might also benefit
也许对你也有好处
from a prescription for anxiety.
行啊 如果你觉得有帮助
Okay, if you think it'll help.
千万别给我开Placinex
Oh, just don't make it Placinex.
我可不想突然变成杀人狂魔
I do not need sudden fits of homicidal rage.
好想你啊
I miss you.
我也想你了呢
I miss you as well.
简直不敢相信我居然这么想Stuart
I can't believe I miss Stuart.
也许我只是怀念生活更简单的时候
I guess I just miss when life was simpler.
加油 Leonard! Leonard!
Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard!
太棒啦 Leonard! Leonard！
记住了 姐妹们 是你自己决定自己的幸福
Remember, girls, you decide what makes you happy,
不是你们没有感情的妈!
not your emotionally withholding mothers!
棒棒哒 Leonard! Leonard 棒棒哒!
Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard!
Leonard 棒棒哒! 棒棒哒 Leonard! Leonard 棒棒哒!
Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard!
真怀念就这样看着他们两个
I really miss this.